Guide to the Arthur E. Scott photograph collection, 1910-1976
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: People, 1910-1976; (Boxes 1-7, 12-22, 26-27, 29-42)
  - Subseries 1.1: Senators, 1930-1976
    - Harrison, Byron P.(Pat), 1920s-1930s (Box 15)
      20 negatives
    - Hartke, Rupert V., 1964 (Box 15)
    - Hatch, Carl A., 1933-1949 (Box 15)
    - Hayden, Carl T., October 16, 1962 (Box 15)
      4 negatives, copy of photograph from Time Magazine, 1912
    - Heflin, James T., 1933 (Box 15)
    - Hickenlooper, Bourke B., 1956-1964 (Box 15)
      35 negatives
    - Hill, Joseph L., 1960s (Box 16)
    - Hitchcock, Herbert E., 1930s (Box 16)
    - Holt, Rush D., 1935-1941 (Box 16)
      20 negatives; includes 34th birthday party
    - Houston, Andrew J., 1941 (Box 16)
    - Hruska, Roman L., 1954-1963 (Box 16)
      80 negatives
    - Hughes, James H., 1937-1943 (Box 16)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., Jr., 1960s (Box 16)
    - Hunt, Lester C., 1949-1954 (Box 16)
    - Javits, Jacob K., 1956-1963 (Box 16)
      40 negatives; includes Jacob K. Javits as senatorial candidate
    - Johnson, Edwin C., 1937-1955 (Box 16)
    - Johnson, Hiram W., 1930s-1940s (Box 16)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1959 (Box 16)
    - Johnston, Olin D., 1950s-1960s (Box 16)
    - Jordan, Leonard B. (Len), 1963-1965 (Box 16)
      60 negatives
    - Keating, Kenneth B., 1959-1965 (Box 16)
    - Kefauver, Carey E., 1957-1960 (Box 16)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1963-1966 (Box 16)
    - Kilgore, Harley M., 1941-1956 (Box 16)
    - King, William H., 1930s (Box 16)
    - Knowland, William F., 1955 (Box 16)
    - Kuchel, Thomas H., 1950s-1960s (Box 17)
    - La Follete, Robert M., Jr., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
    - Lausche, Frank J., 1964-1968 (Box 17)
    - Lee, Joshua B., 1937-1943 (Box 17)
    - Lehman, Herbert H., 1949-1957 (Box 17)
    - Lewis, James H., 1920s-1930s (Box 17)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
    - Logan, Marvel M., 1930s (Box 17)
    - Long, Edward V., 1965 (Box 17)
    - Long, Huey P., 1932-1935 (Box 17)
      8 negatives, funeral
    - Lucas, Scott W., 1940s (Box 17)
      16 negatives
    - Maloney, Francis T., 1935-1945 (Box 17)
    - Mansfield, Michael J. (Mike), 1970s (Box 17)
    - Martin, Edward, 1947-1959 (Box 17)
    - Mathias, Charles M., Jr., 1970s (Box 17)
    - McAdoo, William G., 1930s (Box 17)
    - McCarran, Patrick A. (Pat), 1940s (Box 17)
    - McCarthy, Eugene J., 1964-1965 (Box 17)
    - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1947-1957 (Box 17)
    - McClellan, John L., 1960s (Box 17)
    - McGee, Gale W., 1960s (Box 17)
    - McIntyre,Thomas J., 1964-1966 (Box 17)
    - McKellar, Kenneth D., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
    - McNary, Charles L., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
      14 negatives; includes Vice Presidential campaign of 1940
    - Mead, James M., 1940s (Box 17)
    - Millikin, Eugene D., 1955 (Box 17)
      1 negative; greeting Dwight D. and Mamie Eisenhower at National Airport
    - Miller, John E., 1937-1941 (Box 17)
    - Minton, Sherman, 1935-1941 (Box 17)
    - Morton, Thruston B., 1957-1960 (Box 17)
    - Mundt, Karl E., 1950s (Box 17)
    - Murphy, George L., 1965 (Box 17)
      6 negatives; with Richard M. Nixon
    - Murphy, Maurice J., Jr., 1962 (Box 17)
      1 negative; with Dwight D. Eisenhower
    - Murray, James E., 1940s-1950s (Box 17)
    - Muskie, Edmund S., 1960 (Box 17)
    - Myers, Francis J., 1940s (Box 17)
    - Neely, Matthew M., 1940s (Box 17)
    - Nelson, Gaylord, August 13, 1964 (Box 17)
      1 negative; with Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1950-1952 (Box 17)
    - Norris, George W., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
    - O'Daniel, Wilbert L.(Pappy), 1940s (Box 17)
    - O'Mahoney, Joseph C., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
    - Pearson, James B., 1960s-1970s (Box 17)
      7 negatives; includes Richard M. Nixon, Everett M. Dirksen, Roman L. Hruska, and [Milton R.?] Young
    - Pepper, Claude D., 1930s (Box 17)
      19 negatives
    - Pittman, Key, 1930s (Box 17)
      14 negatives
    - Pope, James P., 1930s (Box 17)
    - Proxmire, William, 1972 (Box 17)
      1 negative; copy from "Today" editorial on William Proxmire's hair transplant
    - Purtell, William A., June 26, 1958 (Box 17)
      1 negative; with John Pastore, Prescott S. Bush, Theodore Green, Norris H. Cotton, Ralph Flanders, Leverett Saltonstall, John F. Kennedy
    - Reed, Clyde M., 1930s (Box 17)
    - Reynolds, Robert R., 1930s-1940s (Box 17)
      3 negatives; includes photograph of letter from Secretary of War Henry Stimson
    - Robertson, Absalom W., August 29, 1960 (Box 17)
    - Robinson, Joseph T., 1930s (Box 17)
    - Russell, Richard B., 1956-1965 (Box 17)
    - Randolph, Jennings, September 11, 1963 (Box 17)
    - Saltonstall, Leverett, February 5, 1960 (Box 17)
      4 negatives, with Tufts College group
    - Schoeppel, Andrew F., 1950s-1960s (Box 17)
      45 negatives
    - Schweiker, Richard S., 1970s (Box 18)
    - Scott, Hugh D., Jr., 1959-1960 (Box 18)
    - Scott, William L., 1970s (Box 18)
      13 negatives; includes copies of old photographs
    - Sheppard, Morris, 1920s-1930s (Box 18)
    - Shipstead, Henrik, 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Simpson, Milward L., August 7, 1964 (Box 18)
      1 negative; includes Barry M. Goldwater and [William E.] Miller
    - Smathers, George A., 1950s-1960s (Box 18)
    - Smathers, William H., 1937-1943 (Box 18)
    - Smith, Ellison D., 1920s-1930s (Box 18)
      12 negatives
    - Smith, Howard A., 1950s (Box 18)
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1950s-1960s (Box 18)
    - Sparkman, John J., 1950s-1960s (Box 18)
    - Stafford, Robert T., 1970s (Box 18)
    - Stevens, Theodore F.(Ted), 1970s (Box 18)
    - Stewart, Arthur T., 1940s (Box 18)
    - Symington, William S.(Stuart), 1950s-1960s (Box 18)
    - Taft, Robert A., 1940s (Box 18)
    - Thomas, Elbert D., 1940s (Box 18)
    - Thomas, John W. E.(Elmer), 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Thurmond, Strom, 1970s (Box 18)
    - Thye, Edward J., 1950s (Box 18)
    - Tower, John G., 1960s-1970s (Box 18)
      4 negatives; with Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Tydings, Joseph, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Tydings, Millard E., 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H., 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Wagner, Robert F., 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Walsh, David I., 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Walters, Herbert S., 1964 (Box 18)
    - Weicker, Lowell P., 1970s (Box 18)
    - Wheeler, Burton K., 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - White, Wallace H., 1930s-1940s (Box 18)
    - Wiley, Alexander, 1950s-1960s (Box 18)
      75 negatives
    - Wiley, Alexander (continued), 1950s-1960s (Box 19)
    - Williams, John J., February 8, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Yarborough, Ralph W., February 19, 1965 (Box 19)
    - Young, Milton R., 1960s (Box 19)
      2 negatives; Senators learning martial arts
    - Senate Civil Liberties Committee, 1930s (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Senators, 1930s-1960s (Box 19)
    - Byrd, Harry F., 1930s (Box 26)
      1 glass plate negative
    - Curtis, Charles, 1910s-1920s (Box 26)
    - Long, Huey P., 1930s (Box 26)
    - Senators, 1920s-1930s (Box 26)
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Includes Hiram L. Fong, Everett M. Dirksen, Robert J. Dole, Gerald R. Ford, Jr.
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Includes Thomas H. Kuchel, Hubert H. Humphrey, Jr., Michael J. Mansfield, Everett M. Dirksen
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Includes Everett M. Dirksen, Barry M. Goldwater, Barry M. Goldwater, Jr., Hiram L. Fong, Hugh D. Scott, Jr., Thomas H. Kuchel, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin, Norris H. Cotton
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Includes Hiram L. Fong, Everett M. Dirksen, Michael J. Mansfield, Joseph S. Clark, William Proxmire, Hugh D. Scott, Jacob K. Javits, Thomas H. Kuchel, Robert P. Griffin, Hubert H. Humphrey, Jr.
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Includes Everett M. Dirksen, Hiram L. Fong, Margaret Chase Smith, Hugh D. Scott, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin, Norris H. Cotton, Thomas H. Kuchel, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Gerald R. Ford, Jr.
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Includes Margaret Chase Smith, Charles H. Percy, Hugh D. Scott, Everett M. Dirksen, Norris H. Cotton, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Includes Michael J. Mansfield, Everett M. Dirksen, Hiram L. Fong, Roman L. Hruska, Robert P. Griffin
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Includes Robert P. Griffin, Edward M. Kennedy, Everett M. Dirksen, Robert F. Kennedy, Margaret Chase Smith, Norris H. Cotton
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Includes Edward M. Kennedy, Norris H. Cotton, Everett M. Dirksen, Hiram L. Fong, Hugh D. Scott, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Includes Hiram L. Fong, Margaret Chase Smith, Hugh D. Scott, Norris H. Cotton, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 31)
      Color slides; includes Everett M. Dirksen, Margaret Chase Smith, Charles H. Percy, Hugh D. Scott, Charles H. Percy, Barry M. Goldwater, Hiram L. Fong, John G. Tower, Michael J. Mansfield, Clifford P. Hansen, Hubert H. Humphrey, Jr., Howard Baker, Edward W. Brooke, III
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 32)
      2 1/4 inch negatives, some color; includes Barry M. Goldwater, Clifford P. Hansen, Hugh D. Scott, Robert F. Kennedy, Strom Thurmond, Norris H. Cotton, Robert J. Dole, Charles M. Mathias, Jr.
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 33)
      Color slides; includes Peter H. Dominick, Everett M. Dirksen, Hugh D. Scott, Milward L. Simpson, Milton Young
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 34)
      Color slides; includes George D. Aiken, Gordon L. Allott, James Boggs, John Cooper, Robert J. Dole
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 35)
      Color slides; includes Strom Thurmond, Hugh D. Scott, Robert P. Griffin, Margaret Chase Smith, John G. Tower, Roman L. Hruska, Michael J. Mansfield, Barry M. Goldwater, Robert J. Dole
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 36)
      35mm, 8x10 inch negatives, some color; includes Hugh D. Scott, Gordon L. Allott, Henry Bellman, Clifford P. Case, Jack R. Miller, Marlow W. Cook, Hiram L. Fong, Barry M. Goldwater
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 37)
      Large format color slides; includes Everett M. Dirksen, Jacob K. Javits, Margaret Chase Smith, Hugh D. Scott, Thomas H. Kuchel
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 38)
      Color slides; includes Robert J. Dole, Strom Thurmond, Hugh D. Scott, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin, Norris H. Cotton, Edward M. Kennedy, Jacob K. Javits, William Brock III, Barry M. Goldwater, Margaret Chase Smith
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 39)
      Color slides; includes Leonard B. Jordan, Clifford P. Hansen, Everett M. Dirksen, Paul J. Fannin, Hiram L. Fong, Barry M. Goldwater, Roman L. Hruska, Jacob K. Javits, Jack R. Miller, Charles H. Percy, Winston L. Prouty
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 40)
      Color slides; includes Hugh D. Scott, Robert P. Griffin, Charles H. Percy, Hiram L. Fong, Strom Thurmond, Barry M. Goldwater
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 41)
      2 1/2 inch negatives, some color; includes Jennings Randolph, Alan H. Bible, Hiram L. Fong, Hugh D. Scott, Charles H. Percy, James Pearson, Robert P. Griffin, Norris H. Cotton, Michael J. Mansfield, Robert W. Packwood, Mark O. Hatfield, Barry M. Goldwater, Strom Thurmond, John G. Tower, Rupert Vance Hartke
    - Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 42)
      2 1/2 inch negatives, some color; includes Hugh D. Scott, Paul J. Fannin
  - Subseries 1.2: Representatives, 1937-1971
    Subseries 1.2 contains photographs of Representatives. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by name and then chronologically within each name.
    - Bush, George H. W., 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Kleppe, Thomas S., 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lodge, John D., 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Miller, William E., 1953-1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - McIntire, Clifford G., 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Includes Margaret Chase Smith
    - Steagall, Henry B., 1930s-1940s (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Includes Jesse Jones, Reconstruction Finance Corporation administrator
    - Wold, John S., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Barden, Graham A., 1950s (Box 19)
      1 negative; portrait
    - Boggs, Thomas H., November 7, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Bonner, Herbert C., 1940s-1950s (Box 19)
    - Brewster, Ralph O., 1930s (Box 19)
    - Burleson, Omar T., 1950s (Box 19)
    - Cannon, Clarence A., April 6, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Cole, William S., 1940s (Box 19)
    - Cooley, Harold D., 1940s (Box 19)
    - Cooper, Jere, 1930s (Box 19)
    - Dingell, John D., 1937 (Box 19)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., August 2, 1967 (Box 19)
      10 negatives; Republican Leadership meets in Gerald R. Ford's office
    - Harter, Dow, 1930s (Box 19)
      1 negative; with Hugo Eckener, Zeppelin Commander
    - McMillan, John L., 1940s (Box 19)
    - Murray, Thomas J., 1940s-1950s (Box 19)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1947-1949 (Box 19)
    - Poage, William R., November 7, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Priest, James P., 1950s (Box 19)
    - Reed, Daniel A., November 7, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Rhodes, John J., October 3, 1966 (Box 19)
      1 negative; with Richard M. Nixon
    - Smith, Howard W., 1930s-1940s (Box 19)
    - Steagall, Henry B., 1930s-1940s (Box 19)
      1 negative; with Jesse Jones, Reconstruction Finance Corporation administrator
    - Teague, Olin E., 1940s-1950s (Box 19)
    - Vinson, Carl, 1940s-1950s (Box 19)
    - Representatives, 1950s-1970s (Box 35)
      Color slides; includes Gerald R. Ford
    - Representatives, 1950s (Box 36)
      35mm negatives, some color; includes Dow W. Harter, W. Sterling Cole
    - Representatives, 1960s-1970s (Box 39)
      Color slides; includes Joel T. Broyhill
    - Representatives, 1960s-1970s (Box 41)
      2 1/2 inch negatives, some color; includes Charles Walen, Jr., Margaret M. Heckler, Henry Smith, Louis C. Wyman
  - Subseries 1.3: Presidents and Vice Presidents, 1910-1976
    Subseries 1.3 contains photographs of Presidents and Vice Presidents. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by name and then chronologically within each name.
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1923-1929 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Dawes, Charles G., 1925-1929 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Includes John J. Pershing
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1940s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 11)
      (1 of 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1940s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 12)
      (2 of 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1940s-1950s (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., 1970s (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Garner, John N., 1933-1941 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Hoover, Herbert C., 1929-1933 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960s (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Mostly funeral photos
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Includes Spiro T. Agnew
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      (1 of 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      (2 of 2)
    - Truman, Harry S., 1945-1953 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Barkley, Alben W., July 28, 1952 (Box 19)
      2 negatives; used on "Time" magazine cover
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1923-1929 (Box 19)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1953-1962 (Box 19)
      200 negatives
    - Garner, John N., 1933-1941 (Box 19)
    - Hoover, Herbert C., 1929-1933 (Box 20)
    - Humphrey, Herbert, 1965-1967 (Box 20)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1960-1968 (Box 20)
    - Lincoln, Abraham, 1960s (Box 20)
      2 negatives; copied from book
    - Kennedy, John F., November 1963 (Box 20)
      1 negative; John F. Kennedy lies in state
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1955-1968 (Box 20)
      100 negatives
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1933-1945 (Box 20)
    - Truman, Harry S., 1945-1953 (Box 20)
    - Misc. Vice Presidents, 1920s-1930s (Box 20)
    - Contest cutouts, Presidents, 1930s (Box 26)
      7 glass plate negatives
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1923-1929 (Box 26)
      32 glass plate negatives
    - Curtis, Charles, 1929-1933 (Box 26)
      14 glass plate negatives
    - Dawes, Charles G., 1925-1929 (Box 26)
    - Garner, John N., 1933-1941 (Box 26)
    - Harding, Warren G., 1921-1923 (Box 26)
      8 negatives; includes Thomas Edison, Henry Ford, Carl Laemmle
    - Hoover, Herbert C., 1929-1933 (Box 26)
      75 glass plate negatives; includes Charles Lindbergh, Juan de la Cierva, Lincoln Ellsworth
    - Taft, William Howard, 1909-1913 (Box 27)
      2 glass plate negatives
    - Wilson, Woodrow, 1913-1921 (Box 27)
      3 glass plate negatives
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., with Senators, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 11)
      Includes Hugh D. Scott, Everett M. Dirksen, John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin, Norris H. Cotton
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., with Senators, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Includes John G. Tower, Robert P. Griffin
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Includes Spiro T. Agnew, Ronald W. Reagan
    - Truman, Harry S. and Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Presidents, Vice Presidents, 1960s-1970s (Box 31)
      Color slides; includes Nelson A. Rockefeller, Richard M. Nixon, John F. Kennedy, Gerald R. Ford, Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Presidents, Vice Presidents, 1950s-1970s (Box 32)
      2 1/4 inch negatives, some color; includes Spiro T. Agnew, Gerald R. Ford, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dwight D. Eisenhower, Richard M. Nixon, Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Presidents, Vice Presidents, 1950s-1970s (Box 35)
      Color slides; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower, Richard M. Nixon
    - Presidents, Vice Presidents, 1970s (Box 36)
      35mm negatives, some color; includes Gerald R. Ford, Richard M. Nixon
    - Presidents, Vice Presidents, 1960s (Box 39)
      Color slides; includes Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Presidents, Vice Presidents, 1960s (Box 41)
      2 1/2 inch negatives, some color; includes Lyndon B. Johnson, John F. Kennedy
  - Subseries 1.4: Notable political figures, U.S. Supreme Court Justices and Foreign Dignitaires, 1921-1971
    Subseries 1.4 contains photographs of Governors, cabinet secretaries, foreign dignitaries, and other important political figures. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by name and then chronologically within each name.
    - Asian diplomatic visit to US, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes Queen of Malaysia, Ferdinand Marcos and Imelda R. Marcos of the Phillipines, King and Queen of Sikkim
    - Blewett, Alexander, Jr., 1960s (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Montana U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Bontrager, D. Russell, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Indiana U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Charles, Prince of Wales and Princess Anne, July 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      includes Tricia and Julie Nixon
    - Farley, James, 1933-1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      includes Pat O'Brien
    - Peterson, Elly, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Michigan U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., III, 1950s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Supreme Court Justices, 1940s (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Valeo, Francis R., Secretary of the Senate, 1960s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 11)
      (1 of 2); Portrait
    - Valeo, Francis R., Secretary of the Senate, 1960s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 12)
      (2 of 2); Portrait
    - Whitmore, Howard, Jr., 1960s (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Massachusetts U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Wilkinson, Bud, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Oklahoma U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Wilkinson, Ernest, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Utah U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Whitney, Wheelock, Jr., 1960s (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Unsuccessful candidate for Minnesota U.S. Senate seat 1964
    - Adams, Sherman, 1953-1958 (Box 20)
      3 negatives; with Jim Haggerty
    - Adenauer, Konrad, May 28, 1957 (Box 20)
      2 negatives; with William Knowland and Lyndon B. Johnson, Richard M. Nixon
    - Alcorn, Meade, 1957-1958 (Box 20)
    - Benson, Ezra, 1953-1961 (Box 20)
    - Black, Hugo, 1937 (Box 20)
    - Biffle, Leslie, 1945-1953 (Box 20)
    - Brown, Fred H., 1939-1940 (Box 20)
    - Brownell, Herbert, Jr., 1953-1957 (Box 20)
    - Bush, George H. W., February 18, 1976 (Box 20)
      1 negative; appointment as Director of Central Intelligence Agency, with John J. Sparkman, Jacob K. Javits, Charles H. Percy, Michael J. Mansfield, Gale McGee, George McGovern
    - Butler, Pierce, 1937 (Box 20)
    - Calver, George W., 1940s (Box 20)
    - Cardozo, Benjamin, 1930s (Box 20)
    - Castro, Fidel, April 17, 1959 (Box 20)
    - Cheng, Chen, 1961 (Box 20)
      3 negatives; with Leverett Saltonstall, George D. Aiken, Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Clark, Charles P., July 14, 1958 (Box 20)
      1 negative; with Spanish Ambassador
    - Clark, Thomas C., 1950s (Box 20)
    - Craig, Malin, October 2, 1935 (Box 20)
    - Cummings, Homer S., 1933-1939 (Box 20)
    - Dern, George, 1933-1936 (Box 20)
    - Donaldson, Bill, 1930s (Box 20)
      3 negatives; with Bill Collins, U.S. Capitol Press Gallery
    - Duke, Joseph C., 1950s (Box 20)
      8 negatives; with Carl Hayden and Ernest McFarland
    - Durkin, Martin P., 1953 (Box 20)
      1 negative; with Mrs. Durkin, Inaugural Ball, Washington D.C. Armory
    - Early, Stephen, 1933-1945 (Box 20)
    - Edison, Charles, 1940 (Box 20)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, October 1957 (Box 20)
      28 negatives; with Prince Philip, Richard M. Nixon
    - Farley, James, 1933-1940 (Box 20)
      40 negatives; includes appearance before committee investigating airmail contracts
    - Flemming, Arthur, June 3, 1960 (Box 21)
      6 negatives; testifying before Congress
    - Gruenther, Alfred, 1950s (Box 21)
      1 negative; civilian portrait
    - Hall, Leonard, January 19, 1957 (Box 21)
      1 negative; smoking peace pipe with North Dakota Indians
    - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1953-1955 (Box 21)
      3 negatives; interviewed by Ron Cochran of CBS
    - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1930-1941 (Box 21)
    - Hull, Cordell, November 13, 1937 (Box 21)
      1 negative; National Press Club Dinner
    - Kerr, Philip, Lord Lothian, 1939-1940 (Box 21)
    - Knox, Frank, July 11, 1940 (Box 21)
      1 negative; sworn in as Secretary of the Navy by Felix Frankfurter
    - Love, John A., 1963 (Box 21)
    - MacCracken, William P., Jr., February 2, 1934 (Box 21)
    - Marshall, George C., 1950s (Box 21)
    - Misc. U.S. Supreme Court Justices, 1930s-1950s (Box 21)
      13 negatives
    - Morganthau, Henry, Jr., 1930s (Box 21)
      1 negative; with Herbert Gaston and James Farley
    - Rabin, Yitzchak, January 28, 1976 (Box 21)
      2 negatives; addressing Congress
    - Reed, Stanley F., 1938 (Box 21)
    - Roberts, Owen, 1930s-1940s (Box 21)
    - Romney, Kenneth, 1931-1945 (Box 21)
    - Roper, Daniel C., 1933-1938 (Box 21)
    - Roy, William, 1938-1948 (Box 21)
    - Sommerfield, Arthur, 1953-1961 (Box 21)
    - Steinle, Roland J., July 17, 1958 (Box 21)
      4 negatives; with Richard M. Nixon, Everett M. Dirksen, other Senators
    - Stone, Harlan F., 1930s (Box 21)
    - Sutherland, George, 1930s (Box 21)
    - Swanson, Claude, 1930s (Box 21)
    - Thorton, Daniel, 1950s (Box 21)
    - Trice, J. Mark, June 5, 1959 (Box 21)
    - Udall, Stewart L., 1960s (Box 21)
    - Underwood, Cecil, October 1960 (Box 21)
      2 negatives; with Louis S. Rothschild
    - Wallace, Henry A., 1933-1940 (Box 21)
    - Warren, Earl, 1953-1969 (Box 21)
    - Woodin, William H., 1930s (Box 21)
      3 negatives; with Cordell Hull, Henry Morganthau, Jr.
    - Woodring, Harry H., 1930s (Box 21)
      29 negatives
    - Cosgrave, William T., January 28, 1928 (Box 27)
    - Hoover, Herbert C., May 2, 1927 (Box 27)
    - MacDonald, Ramsey, 1929-1933 (Box 27)